emotes:
  - name: thumbs_up
    emojis:
      - thumbs_up
    prompt: "Response: give a thumb's up to {author}.\n"

  - name: thumbs_down
    emojis:
      - thumbs_down
    prompt: "Response: give a thumb's down to {author}.\n"

  - name: missing
    emojis:
      - lack
    prompt: "Response: {author} is missing something.\n"

  - name: get_money
    emojis:
      - bread
    prompt: "Response: tell the {author} to get rich or die trying.\n"

  - name: inside_joke
    emojis:
      - its_for_you
    prompt: "Response: the {author} needs to pick up the phone.\n"

  - name: loopy
    emojis:
      - herp_derp
      - blep
    prompt: "Response: {author} is being a goofball.\n"
  
  - name: exhaustion
    emojis:
      - dead
    prompt: "Response: {author} is as tired as a dying monkey.\n"
      
  - name: confusion
    emojis:
      - dafuq
      - herp_derp
    prompt: "Response: {author} is being confusing.\n"

  - name: epic
    emojis:
      - gigachris
    prompt: "Response: {author} is an absolute CHAD"
    
  - name: awesome
    emojis:
      - flawless_victory
    prompt: "Response: tell the {author} they are awesome.\n"

  - name: condemnation
    emojis:
      - judgement
      - flip_off
      - banned
    prompt: "Response: a condemnation of the message from {author}.\n"

  - name: horrible
    emojis:
      - hyper_anti_sheee
    prompt: "Response: the message from {author} is horrible news.\n"

  - name: inappropriate
    emojis:
      - inappropriate
    prompt: "Response: the message from {author} is inappropriate.\n"

  - name: congratulations
    emojis:
      - ole
      - pog
    prompt: "Response: congratulations to the message from {author}.\n"

  - name: excited
    emojis:
      - sheeee
    prompt: "Response: excited by the message from {author}.\n"

  - name: condolences
    emojis:
      - antisheeee
      - low_energy
    prompt: "Response: send condolences to {author}.\n"

  - name: good_answer
    emojis:
      - good_answer
      - wise
    prompt: "Response: you like what {author} said, and that it was particularly clever.\n"

  - name: caught_in_a_lie
    emojis:
      - caught
      - cap
    prompt: "Response: {author} has been caught in a lie.\n"

  - name: delicious
    emojis:
      - drool
    prompt: "Response: you are drooling over {author}'s message.\n"

  - name: suspicious
    emojis:
      - sus
      - terio
    prompt: "Response: {author} is acting suspicious.\n"

  - name: shock
    emojis:
      - shock
    prompt: "Response: you are shocked by {author}'s message.\n"

  - name: laughter
    emojis:
      - lul
    prompt: "Response: you are laughing {author}'s message.\n"

  - name: joy
    emojis:
      - joy
    prompt: "Response: {author}'s message makes you happy.\n"

  - name: shame
    emojis:
      - facepalm
    prompt: "Response: you are facepalming at {author}'s message.\n"

  - name: disappointment
    emojis:
      - disappointing
    prompt: "Response: you are disappointed about {author}'s message.\n"

  - name: confidence
    emojis:
      - stand_by_it
    prompt: "Response: despite facing criticisms, you support {author} with their good idea.\n"

  - name: honesty
    emojis:
      - he_admit_it
    prompt: "Response: An epic turn of events, {author} has to marry their mother-in-law!\n"
